Hi, guys.
Hey, Trixie.
Pen.
Here it is.
Okay, guys.
I have a new showbook, so I have an idea.
I'm going to put it in this book.
I'm gonna put everybody that comes on panel.
I'm gonna tell, like, I'll put with the guy.
I'm gonna, I'll try to log the show,
which I haven't been doing.
So even if it's, I'll have like a record.
Who's been on and, you know,
I don't have an archive, it's unfortunately,
I have to do everything myself.
So it's not that easy, but also we'll do
some fun things with that.
Maybe I'll get some pages on my new showbook started.
Talk too much about it because I don't want to spoil the surprise, but it's gonna be a good one
I don't know it's not that working every other way
Little glow on me. How are you guys doing? I feel like I'm on the moon. I don't know if that works well, but
Hey, I just take a shower
Nails are clean gaudy. Come on. They're clean. They are just clean as a whistle
I know they were kind of bad looking through tobacco. I'll be there when I chat to you and hey, Jamie. How are you?
The link posted up
Yeah, I mean I so I mean like last last stream my phone all the plug is my head over and my phone did
Or my
My microphones died, and so then I wasn't able to like talk and so and then there's I just I
Was just kind of too if you with the phone on the panel so
You got home an hour and a half hour ago. Well, welcome home. So I had this new book. She says be kind. We're back. We're back
Dingle, what's up? This is be kind. This is like the motto of the show
It's like so it's like really easy there's like a way to live your life
The kind of people like don't don't be mean to people in terms of her people at least if you even if you don't try to help people
Don't try to hurt people. I
Do believe that so let's see who we have it and Jamie does in my book
the dingle
Dingles in here as a mar
I'm not gonna take that everyone the tenants every day, but I will just notice like the first time the names
I'm gonna make a major list like a big list, but
You're always okay chat. What's up guys?
Yeah
The right outside your tricks tricks you over there tricks
Thank you D
So this is a nice big big it's like a kind of big book, you know, it's just gonna have a lot of
I had already started it with other stuff, but
Like a start over so
Title page that I have I'll put prairie page the mod down
prairies down
Okay
Thing that is I think I got thing that is yeah, I have thing that is as a member. Yeah
My system's already working. Okay, come back guys. Oh, yep
It's all I mean I try to like to give more creative things like you know Emma had a book
She had his head put her logo put on and stuff and you know she stepped there
I see my name is in her book. She's nice. She crossed it out. She's crossed my name off everything else
But I'd still be in there when someday when she's a hundred years old so or 10,000 years old
She'll look back and say oh remember that
Guys like he wasn't so bad
He made a be made one bad diddy party joke and I threw in the whole relationship. That's not foolish of me
But we all make mistakes, right? I think I have some past life stuff with those two. Maybe I'll be married to her or something
I'm not sure. Okay. So let me see
My chat
I'm just trying to pin the link you called me remember. Oh
Yeah, no, you know
It's a better be a big dick or a little
Yeah, but I think a big dick is always better
Good hand. Okay. Okay. One second. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
I'm doing okay. How are you tonight?
I'm very well after a very tough week, but I'm here
You tell me because there's your birthday and that's something you don't show if we go in your booth. I'm sorry
No, that was last week and oh
Oh, yeah, and you are my time I'll blitz together. I
Was it yeah?
It's not gonna be nice. I'm a kind person
They know is extremely nice and how deeply appreciated. Oh
You're very welcome. It's nose to get off my sits
So yeah, my oh your monkey valley ice. You're using the Mach Machiavellian
Dark triad on me. Oh, I was there. I was ever with you
You're rock. No mad. Tell me about your tough week, bro
I'm absolutely not
Fucking freak this little faggot came up being said hey
I had a rough week. Shut the fuck up. You don't know what a rough week. Yes, my man
Don't ever come up here talking shit like that
You don't know
I want to hear about it
When you said he doesn't feel like talking to me about this full of fucks tough week
Very wise to discuss such things and a baby was trauma. Maybe it was traumatizing me with personal
You don't know so he's like a
Making fun of humanity broke as this motherfucker's a small piece of shit. Listen to the way he talks rough week
You know how to rough week in your life, brother
Well, I mean compared to you or no at least tell me about it since you said I had a rough week
Tell me about your off week. I think the wall happened that made your week so rough
The roughest week for me
Will not equal to no not equal to shut the fuck up
You're such a loser. Are you the guy that sits in the back of the triangle that drives itself?
That's you right
That's you with the big muscles and the guy that talks to site like he's his father and there's a car that drives itself
That's you with the rough week
Wow
So tell me about your week that made us so rough
Get me to use
Well, you're not gonna get to hear it friend
No shit because you'll spoke he's a shit line through your teeth
Okay, Alex either it was a really really bad weekend. He just wanted to talk about him
He can't answer the question. Yeah, he's holding his cars close to his chest. That's what that's what a great monkey belly would do, right?
I just want to hear about his rough week, man. He just said he had a really rough week. I just want to hear about it
He doesn't want to talk, but he
So why say it
Why say it if you don't want to talk about it. He just said I had a really rough week. What happened. I don't want to talk about it
What?
Who know I
Don't I really don't know. I mean I could guess the I know that's why I'm asking him a site
But he's not gonna
We he's not he's like he's never gonna answer you in a million years
He's not gonna give you one detail or if he does it's not gonna be the truth. All right, cool, man
I mean, this is I mean, I guess I can just I just know how I already operate
No, you know, if you have a rough week, you know, the good thing is no matter how bad it is
If it's really if it's really bad, it's really bad as bad as they can get they only get better
You know what's out there in the world for a little kids are starving homeless
That's a rough week brother. Well, tell me about your rough weekend rogue. No, man
Well, I think that every single one of us operates within our own context and the concept like of roughness is
Very subjective. So you're retarded. You're retarded stop talking bro and the story. Just shut the fuck up
So every experience we have
Context over a week. Oh, shut the fuck up
We case my man
the
No, here's what here that means out is it means that all those are individuals and so we all have our own
Lens so we look at things individual, but we also like to compare ourselves
Shut the fuck up. I'm asking this answer about his rough week
Don't try to intervene and like make sense of it. Let the man explain his rough week
Don't talk to me like that on my show. I won't talk to you like that motherfucker. I'm asking this answer about his rough week, bro
Okay, and you got to have you ask the answer and then I try to you know, you know, just give a little insight into
Objectivity subjectivity and that kind of thing and then you just have to be on my own show Alex
It's not your show Alex. You don't talk to me like that on my show. Okay. I'm not gonna let you do it
it's inevitable to feel a little bit cared for when somebody cares that much about your rough week
Alex I mean he's in bed I mean he's in bed to be fair he does think you're like a hundred people so
he is it's like a lot of people who he's interested in but you know I know it's just I know it's like
it's not but you clearly it sounds like he's intoxicated so he cannot use his mind but you I think you
understood what I was saying that like that concept of roughness is very subjective
Right. He's talking about like little kids in african on having food
Yeah, yes that that is but of course
Yeah, but I mean it'd be fairly not many americans experience that
100%
Everyone's blessed it of having a challenging week. I used it within the subjectivity of my own
Yeah, your lens is your own perspective. It's your own your lens. Yeah, you're a parrot to perhaps even Alex's life
Like I may have had an amazing week that he could never get to experience
but just as far as what I
Navigate week after week. It was simply a challenging week
That does not mean that it was a saddening week or an angering week
There were challenges that were overcame and that's it and it's fine to have challenging weeks
like it's part of having a career, it's part of being an adult, it's absolutely okay.
Like, we're not in a competition of who is able to exercise the utmost,
what will be appropriate for it.
I say like you know, it's like it's like the the the oneness it's like that's like seeing everybody else as an aspect of yourself
So relating to everybody in some way it's like we can we we all can but
We're also all individuals that we really don't experience like we can like feel or know what they might be going through
But we can't really ever be inside somebody else's mind, you know
And it's like we and we shouldn't because we have our own minds to worry about we shouldn't be worried about
Rather than trying to help them and stuff, but I think that I think that is laughing in a sense. Okay, I
Think that the more that we are able to strengthen ourselves physically mental emotionally
And if we choose a path of service
Then the more that such strength is able to be channeled onto the well-being of others
Right, and that's like a big thing like a lot of them especially in America
We tend to be a little bit individualistic which can translate to maybe selfish and more interested in ourselves
But it's like there's so many you know, there's a lot of people that need help and
That are struggling and then we can't help and it's like we shouldn't just walk by
Some people that we can
Possibly help because we're so worried about ourselves. We need to like if that's the thing
It's a coming kind of coming out of our own selfishness and opening ourselves up to other people when we get you know
You want to be the Santa Claus instead of just always get the gifts on Christmas day
We want to be the one that it gives to get sometimes, right?
100% yeah, absolutely
Otherwise works. Yep. Well, that's why
Chatting with you, I think that you have a very very kind heart
I think that we're not super intoxicated, you know, pretty bright mind.
Thank you.
And you present like a lot of interesting conversations.
So it's, you know, hence why I'm drawn into this.
And okay, you know how I said earlier on that I was manipulating your relationship with
If I told you you would laugh you would laugh and you won't believe it when you laugh a lot
It's very very silly and funny
But believe me. It's not
It's by no means malicious in any way. Oh, it's just funny. It's just funny to you including
I've made you laugh without you knowing it was me
mm-hmm
Yeah, I mean I got a lot like that's why I say I don't even mind like you know if there's different few people
I different characters. I don't really as long as they're they come on and they're they play the character well
They're entertaining and they they maintain their characters. It's not so obvious. I mean
Alex you're a fool Alex stop it. Oh
You're having one of those nights Alex. You just need to like maybe just like you know take a little
Take a little you know break break heat from from my my piano. Okay, cuz it's like you're just you're you're you're giving power
Hungry you're by me of Napoleon. It is most insane. It's not a good. Look Alex. Okay, just calm down
Okay, Alex, it's all gonna be okay. Okay, but don't talk about don't talk about my show like that. Okay, you're not supposed to as a member
Okay, well if you're a pure true member
Maybe you're just well, I think that there's to an extent a level of possessiveness by some people over these channels and
Over some streamers. I think what you're witnessing is a level of that guy
I think partly being intoxicated, but he's definitely exercising possessiveness over you
They he's like that attention that psyche has to share belongs to me and the fact that he's not the
Full recipient of it makes him very angry. And that's why we're witnessing this behavior
I mean, I mean, I'll I mean, you know
I always let him on the I was like usually I'm on the panel like he's in the chat
You know, I keep you know telling everybody. Oh, he's a good guy. You know, he's uh,
He's he's like a character. He's not really like that. But you know, I I just don't know now. He's
He's screaming that I'm I'm I'm part of this syndicate that's trying to take down my show
I mean, it doesn't make any sense. I like it seems like there's like theological fallacies word. I mean, it's a nice thing
Let me say I'm Tony
And I stage this whole thing
Now wouldn't that be something? Okay, but no no Alex
It's like a lot of different people. Maybe it's like the same demonic spirit possessing some of the people that after me
But it's not
Conspiracy that people are knowingly doing. I don't think I mean that'd be just
And also I don't think like some of the people that you are cute you're like they oh Michael look like was him on his guy
Michael can barely turn turn on his phone. I mean, it's like it's not like you can't he's not gonna be figuring out how to do all these voice changers
Yeah, he's there feeding his dog on with the volume speaker on half the time. I mean, it's like so it's not I
Don't know. It just doesn't make sense. It doesn't make dollars. It doesn't make sense
But Alex, you know what you keep going you write that report. I want to read that report
I'm gonna I'm gonna laugh but there might be something. Yeah, just use a highlighter on something that you actually like believe in your heart, okay?
That's all I have to say about that
And okay
He like
Because when I use Waymo, you know that the app where you can just order, right? He's so I
Got him. He's a fucking stupid that he thinks is my own corner
He keeps thinking that, oh, life is so hard when you have a car that drives itself.
It's like, first time it's a nap, dude, I'm paying to ride in that vehicle.
But he thinks that I'm like fucking Batman, that I just get driven around by AI.
And he hates it and meanwhile meanwhile he's sitting in a in a Batman costume in a basement like a bad case
You know with all these computers around, you know
Yeah, he's half he's half the Joker. I don't know. I don't know. It's like I feel like I'm dealing with a
Marble villain or I don't know
Yeah, I mean, it's like it's like, you know, if he's least scared of what he might be it's like, I hope he's a cop
Maybe there's some maybe maybe some maybe some police protection around otherwise. He's just an insane criminal
Well, I don't know funny. It's so it's a very funny character. This guy plays I'd like
And it's like oh, yeah, so if you don't play characters fine
just like it's like they're just like, you know
No, where the character ends and you begin and hopefully I can get to know maybe both and I can like
Interact with the character and and with you
I'm talking about not just you but everybody, you know, I'd like to I do like to
Kind of like find who's really in the troll usually. They're not bad people
I see a lot of people with animals like if you love people that are just caring people and you know that maybe just have like a little
Troll blood in them and like to play around the
People with them that are really they're really harmless that there's some people that are just harmful there is attacking and I mean
They're doing those crazy
witness like that's
That's something that I didn't even know existed. Did you see that guy that got?
Yeah, yeah the streamer that did that thing that you
Yeah, I know I mean see people can smack a snap especially, you know
He was pretty he was doing pretty well on YouTube, you know, like you know
Like, you know, free, like, you know, he had like a freaking thousand members or something.
And so, you know, and just to have someone mess with it, you know, just someone vindictive
is just trying to bully, you know, and it's like, that I was listening to a reading tonight
and ladies like, and she's like, well, you know what, she's like, she's like.
Sometimes people they people see you as perfect then they they want to see they want to that's that that's there's nothing wrong with that
There's something and so they didn't they want to
Yeah, exactly
But I'm not but I'm not I'm like such that the thing is like if I was perfect
I'd be like, oh, you know, I'd be like, oh you plebeians and like, you know, just like lat like no
It's like I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm imperfect. I'm just like what I'm another one of the humans like I'm another like everybody everybody is
You'll have these complicated minds. We have these we have these desires. We have these emotions. We have our senses
We have our hunger and our drive. We have a lot of things
And we have then we have complicated with a billion people that are kind of like us, but not us. And so, you know
So it's a miracle we get along as well as we do
inevitably
success
tensor inspire envy on
right
Yeah, and that's the whole even like even if you have not done anything negative to them at all
They're going to start developing a big like a vendetta against you because you're successful and they're not
So I know all their demons against you because they see you as the one to take down
And even if you don't even know who the fuck they are. Yeah, I could be a kid better
I think there is like some kind of like
Even if like even in a gang like so again, right? There's actually it's not like a bunch of people
It's actually one mind with a lot of like in the one mind is like it's like a hive mind
It turns into a hive mind or they all
Developed like to say their the brain will actually like morph into each other and it's almost like they just turn into each other
Sometimes they look like each other. I mean, it's crazy. You know, who knows if it's based on reincarnation
One of the most I think one of the most dangerous weapons is influence
Hey, it's being able to there's a book that I read by
Arizona State
Professor Robert Saldini is just influence and it's so extremely interesting
because
As humans, the ability to influence others becomes an amazing strategic advantage under any situation.
So influence is one of the most dangerous weapons that a human can employ.
And that is, you know, as you said, like a gang mentality or a hive mind, they're all influenced by the same thing.
the same towards the same goal, which was and what are they what what what? Yeah, I'm sorry go ahead
Which was influenced by whoever you know?
Chose to put that in their mind and look but look at look but look at like so so in order to in order to influence you have to have
one-on-one or another thing you have to either you have to you have like innate trust and like and
They just think they they they are they they know you're gonna be right. They just they trust you and
That that's that can be a part of influence or they can fear you and then you can scare them and influence them a negative way
It's always I think it's always better to be
respect respected a little other than respected that is to be fear right it's
like a hundred percent and we have the fear of gaining influence especially in
our society is bartering is entrepreneurship is simply let's say
offering a service that genuinely benefits others like I have the solution
to your problem and
Then they inevitably will respect you and that's how like word-of-mouth marketing occurs
But they just bartering it's a constant opportunity to arrange people's trust and respect and
You know you some people who use that to further political careers or different things look at Trump
Like Trump as a businessman. So like the ultimate barter who became president
not a politician. So, bartering is an extremely useful form of exercising influence, you know,
it depends on what you're bartering with, but it can be done in an absolutely honest
way. If you're truly helping people and caring for them, and you solve their problems, then
Like let's say let's say a person is great at fixing cars
Right, and you don't know anything about cars and your car breaks down then but that person really appreciates you
You did some bartering with them so you can reach out to him be like hey look my car is broken down
It needs this this or that whatever and that person is definitely gonna go out of their way to help you
That's right humanity at work
And a fun thing we yeah, we have it because we do you have a we do you have like a women's league is that?
I think Ben Franklin had this it was some of kind of a fact Ben Franklin or maybe Andrew Carnegie
But it's like when we when when someone does the favor even we don't ask for the favor when someone does the nice first
We have like this thing called reciprocity where we just we once
Yeah reciprocity where we we once said like it's not because it's like it's just a feel right just to take and that's also like you know
I think it's important just you have a energy exchange. That's the bartery thing. It's like, you know, because
Like when I said that I had a rough week
I said like what I meant was I was presented with some challenges that thankfully
Where overcome they were overcome and it led to extreme gratitude from people which leads to
more opportunity and more business and more money
so
Like that's why like it's it's challenging within my own subjective view of what a challenge is
But if I'm in the business of solving challenges
They perhaps a good week needs to be challenging. It's just a matter of whether I could overcome it or not
Yeah, I went does not kill you makes you stronger as Nietzsche said and it's you know, so it's and it's like it that really
It's the experience that helps us to become wiser and to grow and to perform better and we can always
Have more self-awareness and change for the better. I believe that. All right, so because you are such a
Good human being but I almost feel like by sharing this. I'm gonna fuck up the whole joke
But I guess yeah, I guess it's time I
Guess it's time because they you're very very very
Well-deserving human, but you know big Nisha
One big niche. Oh my god. Yeah
Well, I didn't I didn't enjoy that character. Yeah, you just make me laugh it was yeah
She's funny, you know, and I know I get kick out of that
I do I used to go to Emma's and go under as Nicholas Cage and Elon Musk
And I went in there and she was laugh and it's like and then
And he didn't and I didn't tell it was me for a long time. I told her like you know after we
Separate or whatever
I meant no harm or offense at all. I said
Because I was just big nation that's all I meant, okay
Yeah, and I
Had dreams up big Nisha back went to like
I did
Again, the black I did I know Jamie
Alexander's in shock Alexander Alexander feels I was in you didn't figure out big Nisha. Did you Alex?
That was the one you could have gotten
You didn't get that one the whole thing. Yeah
Like, I kept adding more and more and more and more and more lower, but, you know, it
was all in the terms of making you and the chat laugh.
That was a complex joke, but I thought it was so funny how you were like, oh, Big Nisha,
and then when you remember when you drew her, it was the biggest thing.
And then she was like darling
It was great
That's a good one. I like it. I mean that's you have to kind of maybe I don't let me consider that trolling really
I think that's just like you know, it was a character and
You know, it was a it was a nice. It was actually a nice character, you know
I hope she's gonna be like an inside joke. Yeah
Let the chat. Yeah
Yeah, everybody nobody's howl anybody that you know, you know
Like a card that we can play when there's like random ass brand new people then big initial appear
But yeah, big mission remember when she was kidnapped by her cousin Devonte. Yeah, could call the gumbo
Yeah
Then I was like, I was like, I was like, why don't you escape? Oh my god. I forwarded you woke up. Oh, no
well
Oh, Alice is not leaving thing that it Alice is doing right there, please. He's
You know you're not separate Alice from the show
Alice had I was like the niche and now now he's questioning sexuality again and first and 40 diamond now big niche
I mean, it's like and he was he thought he was safe of big niche because
Yeah, he felt safe
Big mission made him feel safe
But now he realized it was me alone. So so that's how loyal of a viewer. I've been because you know
Big mission was almost like every day. Yeah, I know I didn't see you for weeks, but then she she was there every day
Dude, that's been me. Yeah, you really gotta do that into a character. You're gonna keep her. Okay, good
Yeah, it's like, you know, she never hurt anybody. She was very sweet and friendly
Hey, yeah, that's it. Like that's that's my big fucking
social engineering
on for for for making everybody hopefully a little bit more entertained
That's it. Mm-hmm. Yeah, well, it's not just well
Yeah, come listen what that's not again in your chat. You can be creative and like, you know
If you're gonna really come on all the counts you might as well, you know
Create an interesting story
you know kind of like
Chat with me and say I didn't think this was a mod
She won't be anymore, but yes, you was the one. No, but
But there's no big issues. No, yeah, it's you if you do something wrong
okay, I
Never like I never ever timed anybody out or anything unless
like actually like you asked it and you like please I never I never I never had a complaint about
Big Misha yeah she's just a darling you know
Just loves everybody. She likes to make her gumbo. She cares about don't know remember when you broke your bike and shit
And I was giving you actual advice. I was saying you just gotta align the fucking handlebars with the front wheel
Mission is that I fixed bikes. I was like, what a brother sauce one is a well is because she does for don't know all the time
I'm lucky. Yeah
I'm looking at my book.
I have some interesting things written in it, but.
It says Satan is a symbol of attaining the number nine
crowned by the zero, possessing one and eight master
and all in between two, three, four, five, six, seven.
I don't know.
And it says AO alpha omega, alpha epsilon omega.
Alpha is one and omega is.
zero
The other I don't know. I don't know. I'm just reading looking at this crazy book
Most of Britain about Satan also
Okay
It was like I was basically watching like a lot of like, you know
Metaphysical shows and just like taking notes and stuff or I'd find stuff and I just like recopy it down here
Um, and then so I just but I just wrote a few pages now. It's now it's got everyone's name
I'm putting to your name in the chat. I'm gonna I'm reworking this book. So
See Alex is
Saw saw the awards
Pack or the sal view of the whack pack. He's the nucleus that keeps all the get oh, please
Alex
What's stuck in his is his pants in the morning way, so
Maybe he is he's full of horseshit that's why he is blue. I don't know. I like I like out the
Too much tonight. He's calling me
retarded
And then it's my show. I don't like to go in there. No one ever called Jerry Springer
Retarded on his own show. I mean they just say Jerry
All you're allowed to say is psyche like I thought you're gonna say from now on though
No one hearing complaints when the guy is like super drunk. He just like likes to talk shit
Like many others. I don't think he's even
Doesn't sound that drunk. I mean, I had like a beer. I had two beers so far and it's like I'm
Okay, I don't know. He seems like he's
I thought that's luring or anything. It's not like something's big or
Interesting how he he's so like a clearly anybody with a barely rational mind will know that he's not
Police at all, but he's like such a big fan of the police. It's a it's really
It's pretty rare
Wait, he said he got he said he got like
But what do you say 25 years in prison for having a like a 15 kilos of cocaine or something and that I
Don't know you worked out some kind of deal. I don't I just don't think that they would like you know
Hey come work for us that I don't think they would do that. They probably say oh, let's be the format on the
On the actual thing that if you actually get that pass in life you'll be talking about it publicly on there
Oh my god. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, this is like if you believe in his theories
He wouldn't be just like sharing them all over like just giving it giving away all the everything you know
Oh, yeah, he's hit off everybody that he thinks is in that everyone
Deny it now
Those like your change the name of the group, you know
Sort of new group and it was be gone. He's he's already blown the cover. All right, so
Okay, Alex, what are you doing? It's like it didn't it's really didn't help. I mean, it's like just
Yelling it. He actually thought I was
Behind the whole thing at the end. He's like, why are you why are you doubting me? I was like, it sounds stupid, but
But I think you know those characters make some of the streams pretty entertaining
Because where the fuck else in every day life are you gonna come across a character like that?
Like I cannot think any any time in my life where I will come across a guy like that ever so it makes it
Very and the problem is that he's not like a big niche it. He's not like a like a
Created character like that's his real self
Alex either at you find either at like home or in a mental asylum or
It's like one of those three definitely mental asylum, I think will be yeah
With a fucking straight jacket a padded wall
And then then later on fast forward three hours of the day, oh, I'm sorry
I just wanted to say hi to psyche and go into battle
They but those people you know, that's why it this is one thing we've used that you
And it's not with you so much, but like with beta that beta I think
Allows a lot of this stuff to get into her actual everyday person of life
And I've had this conversation with her where I have like I don't think I think that you need to have a sense of
detachment when you do these streams and
Not be affected by the things that people say about you or blah blah blah
Like hey, how it's up. What up? What up? What up?
I got yeah, you know, you know, I wrote, you know, rogue if you talk to really in the panel before I talk to rogue nation
But I think I remember him could have been a supporter from a one. I'm not sure. Oh, good morning, mister
What what is his name?
Well, it's a it's a easy
We haven't met it's nice to meet you
So so Alex was walking tonight again, I hear you're talking about Alex
Yeah, I mean he was calling D. D. Electra a dumb bitch, and I know and he was saying that she was Piranha
Which is ridiculous. I mean it's so ridiculous. I know
I don't need to explain and then he was the name was saying calling me a retard until I mean it's shut the f up
on my piano, I was like, just
I had to kick him off several times and I don't regret it
Let me know you back up. I like you Alex. I mean, I never missed everything
Dead that happens. I think a few beers earlier in the day that I fall asleep early then I wake up
We late at night like oh, yeah, I was wondering why you were you starting to go to some live later and later like in
My evenings you're gonna
I've been thinking also like about maybe cutting down and I think seven days is like, you know
I just been just working like really hard and it's like, you know
It's probably better just for you in the show to take a day like at least one day off a week and then come back
The fresh and you know excited and there you go
But I am I'm kind of a workaholic when it comes to the show, you know people say it's
When you do what you love for living, it's an art itself to remain in love with it.
And sometimes that means creating a degree of distance between you and it, so you learn
to miss it.
And just like you said, you come back to it, re-energize, re-invigorate it, and you simply
miss it.
But if you're doing it every single day, the only result out of that, even if it's your
Yeah, but I mean, I think it is probably, I mean, that was one of the piece of advice
I was told when I started streaming was like, I probably don't need to really do it anymore
since I'm already at the monetized phase and so I don't really need, I don't really need
the hours, but you know, they said, what you're going to need to do is, I forgot what I was
Your other say I don't know. I'm a little bit accumulate a certain amount of hours. Oh
Yeah, well, yeah, you need what I mean. I don't need to do that anymore
And so I can I can take a break. I can take it, you know, but I do I do like to but I did
Oh the advice was to stream every day though. It's the advice I was given was
Speak insistence you every day even because even if they some days are good some days aren't
If you're consistent that's good for the algorithm, that's that's I mean, but I think that I've been on so much that now
It's probably bad for the algorithm that I end so many shows
But you you have to put yourself first as a human being your physical mental and emotional
Well-being before any algorithms at all. All right, you don't need to become a subject of the algorithm
you simply put yourself first make sure that you're happy and healthy make sure your personal
algorithm is running and then and then you can synchronize it with the professional algorithm
but never let the professional algorithm just completely ruin your personal algorithm
Yeah, I mean, I do I am taking care of myself. I clean my whole this whole room
I'm gonna be cleaning the rest of my house that you know, I mean dance and
You know, I'm getting more sleep. I've been drinking a less and I've been
Try not to fall asleep on the panel. I don't think I have I just have but I have listened to it because you know
He doesn't even have any we I have I do have weed. I have I have like the vape
I'm gonna see how much the flaps in it. We see. Oh
All right, I'm out. Yeah, you got a little half of a flip some Marcy
Yeah, I know but the algorithm is like yeah, you can say that you know
Oh, that's not important
It's like at the end of the day, it's really not but it does you know
I like I saw when I met Benny get like a hundred people in his chat
He has shadow band and mess with the algorithm and it's some bad way and then that way has they hardly even his chat
And that's they kind of like and it's hard to like
Hanged that around I don't know so I say I just like to be consistent to make sure I'm checking it with people that I know
I know
But you need to
It's part of your responsibility if you're taking this professionally to remain passionate
about it.
And that requires some distance from it.
So you could be like five days on and like at least two days off to be with your cats
to go out and about like to maybe like do some type of fitness, do something that creates
some contrast from your professional.
Doing a lot of sober and doing a lot of drunk
Well, yeah, I mean, it's like, you know, when I forget too much weed I get too tired
Or then I say if my sleep schedule is all messed up then I might get too drunk
But then it's like when I'm sometimes when I'm doing sober streams in the mornings
I'm a little bit hungover so I don't I'm so it's like I think I think I think I'm big
I'm trying to think about my body chemistry. So I feel the best, you know, because I'm a
You know, I'm pretty kind of just a bit sensitive to any kind of any kind of chemical
Smoke weed a lot fail to recognize that when they don't have it they get moody as fuck
Yeah, I learned this via dating chicks that smoke weed and when they don't have the week they are
very hostile and mean I wake up like that I wake up like that
I'm gonna fucking weed that up yeah yeah yeah and then I
saw it on psyche a few days ago when like I think he tried to stop the weed or
he didn't have it or whatever and then he was just like in a bad mood
because it makes it makes scientific
You got to think about this you got you're running a panel
Usually hi, I was appealing well
You usually hire drunk, and then that day you're sobered out and you got a bunch of assos pissing you off
And you know, there's no
Oh
No
Well, I didn't like what he was saying in the last stream, and I don't know this guy's with the same thing
It's like Alice will me in the last stream, but I don't know why but it's that right my my head pulls it out
But what was he doing and then the other guy didn't confirm that he's thinking until I'm sure it's the guy Tyler
I think he's in it. He's gonna tell he's seen there as they go on
how it's drinking moonshine and stuff like that, and then Alice was screaming,
oh no, he's not, he's, I don't, I don't, don't scream that out of my chat unless it's like verified because that's, it's like, it's not, it's not...
Yeah, oh jevato is verified to be an n-word bumma on my page three years ago. He'd be on um people's podcast recently
He goes crazy with that word, but they let him rock, but
Oh jevato, I went through I already went through MC nemesis. You know a million times. I can't
Same guy the same guy. Yeah
Same guy as the second profile
You're caught empty nemesis. Oh my god
And how did I know that see Alice, this is the real power and I knew I figured out Alex and I didn't even know I did
Literally figured it out. Oh g vital is emcee nemesis same person big figured it out three years ago any admitted there on page
We used to call him Papa Smurfs. He should come in under the name Papa Smurfs
Okay
Well, Papa Smurf, time to go back to Gargamel, okay?
And, uh...
I mean, how you, um...
You'll have a problem with the yeah, oh no no Michael. Come on. Let's not talk about that
I'm gonna talk about that never sit and boss it or different. Okay. Okay. I think that is I mean
They can trust me here minute on my pinch you mean
But yeah, but then like that I had this guy Dougie Dion and then and then and then every two of us I really I think that's Doug D in the chat
I was like, I don't think it's Doug D and then the Doug D in the chat started commenting. Oh
Yeah, okay, so it seemed like it was him and then I talked to the real Doug D and Doug
That's not me. I mean, so I don't know if it's a coincidence or
It doesn't matter. It's like, you know, just uh,
Which was the real one you got the real one locked in that's it the real ones like yeah, the real ones like there's an older man and uh
She looks kind of like Don Vito and Ben Marchers uncle. I don't know. He's like a nice like
You know like they'll I think Massachusetts or something accent who just dropped off. Let me see. Okay. No
Yeah, so
Nemesis I know I know I know it's your brother
Whatever if Bartos Nemesis, he's like the greatest character actor ever
I know that's what I'm saying
We're gonna be too many some of these people too much credit for like house how they really think you know acting is a big towel
It's not easy to like
You know do all that but you know, it's possible some people can you know, I know an Howard Stern
He had a couple writers who could do these prank calls with like several different voices and voice changers and they sound like a female male
I mean there's just and they were just starting to go crazy and I don't feel like
They do both of them like to ask for rap battles. Do both of them like rap battles
That's Alan Richard. Yeah, I guess
No, be as long as requested rap battle, but whenever I was
She likes it, but she sucks. She said, oh
Big she's just not good at the rabbit. Oh, she's
Close you know as good at rap is Alisa Alisa is like she sings like song pepper like with a song pepper slice
She sings it's so good. She sings some other rap songs like contemporary ones
She's like a gangster
The thing at least that works out because she's afraid like nice little petite body or she's
Natural natural
Of course snapbacks which they can eat and do anything and just stay that it's called snapback. Let's not right back to it
They give you have a baby and in a week later. You look at them. Be like, did you have a kid snapback bitch?
Yeah, you know if you work Saturday night
I don't you know, I don't think she works that I think that she's naturally like this like me
I'm skinny. She's I think she's naturally a natural figure. Then she's very tall
I think she's about five five eight five nine maybe five ten
She looks like about six fish and powers over this
Mm-hmm and
Yeah, I mean it's like she's really beautiful. She has a perfect makeup, and I love her clothes. I think she doesn't do it's like the same thing
I don't do but guess what it is the nails
Like she everywhere like she like she showed her nails and like she let her sister put these stickers on her system
So these like pyramid scheme sticker nails, right?
But you put on and they were all just to put him on all crooked and she's like look everywhere. It's just kind of fun
I think you can put them on better than
So Michael's in the chat. I like my glory you Michael. It's not Michael L. Who who do I think he's uh, he's not Michael
but he is a
He's not he's not black, but he does sound black quantum experience quantum experience. Okay. He's I
think
And you have the video still okay
Dubs Dubs still got the video. Okay. Yeah, cuz he's talking to me. That's why he's talking. It was so crap
So I didn't want to over talk you so I wrote in the comments. I'm sorry. I just put this beer up first
Getting warm. Hold on. Oh
Yeah, that at least a chick is really hot in my opinion
I mean, I've seen her with like I think she might be a different type of words like I just don't see her like I she's been engaged to a couple of gay guys and
You know
I think she was with captain content who's like a
I
They what the fuck? They what? Yeah, he was with
He was with her for a year
Like what is why are I already I already ate her budget either pussy in there, but I'm not sure. Yeah, but that like what does like
What the fuck those are those are all gay guys. Oh
Yeah, I mean it's like Andy dick and even Ben you was kind of like, you know, but there's videos on her
channel, I don't I think it's you know, maybe she's a kind of woman that likes to be like hyper dominant
You you want to eat that pussy, right? No, and I will I think physically I would
Like, I would like to explore her body, but the thing is that by doing that, you're giving her power.
By doing that, you're giving her power.
So, like, I wouldn't...
Saki loved it, that one.
That was a good cover, right Saki?
Yeah, I was giving her power.
Because you will be giving her power, and I think...
If you...
That gets turned on by being, like, denied.
Like yes, she wants to command all these gay guys to eat her pussy and things like that
But the ultimate trend for a bitch like to for a woman like that is to get told what to do
They that bitch on a leash until her walk
Well, you know what she has a couple colors when one's name is Spartan one's name is mayor
They call in and they're just like
Really cool. Okay, so are you
Well, she probably like being dominated
Put your thumb right on your against your head, okay
Because she's now associated men which is like dominating them, but at the same time look at the men she's dominated
Like
Welcome to the stage. You're on the show
Welcome to the stage psyche, you know, I've been here a couple times. Okay, I'm reading for me
I just I'm just I just some people use different names. I have to be careful. Hey, what's up? How are you?
That's a I have a small little screen. I can't really see that
You didn't look the AI, you didn't look the AI, if you were staying real still, just go still.
I know, that's what I was thinking, I was like, you look at it, that's what I was thinking.
You look at it, you see everybody, you look at AI.
I had a guy that came on and I was like, can you say hi?
And then his hand went up real quickly, just like that, like a palm, and then it was gone.
I was like, okay.
I let him on he was a pop for a bummer. So not nothing. Just watch out for those
Guys, you should write down if you're you know has a show with streaming art
You should write down the the name that comes up under the verify user because they usually
Well, they usually don't change as I've noticed as you can
That part don't change. Yeah, you can't you can't alter that and it got certain letters
We're sorry people. Yeah, I was funny. You didn't look over there when you froze it the head things just now, dude
That you killed it
It's like that, it's like really quick, it was just like that, so.
The one from them from what was it? Was it TV show once upon a time?
Wizard of Oz
Wizard of Oz and the Lord of the Rings
No, no, no, you gotta watch um, you gotta watch once upon a time. He's even better than there
Grimm's fairy tales originally, but I know it's I know it's
I know but I
It's kind of like gold
Yeah, I was but I was like thinking of golem
right. And so, um, that's the
big blow to the rings.
No, he got, no, he got the
wheel that that threads gold.
Rob, you got the wheel that
threads gold.
Yeah, I guess he does.
Then he would, uh, he would,
uh, spin it every night for
that woman and then
This year
Like you'll like once upon a time psyche in that
It's an animated I've done years ago the animated it's kind of like a Disney movie, but it's like a different company
And it's a really it's pretty cute movie. I'm not sure if it's the same one. Maybe I'm not sure
TV shows a TV show. Yeah
Those are Peter Peter Pan's pops and somebody else's you've not even found that one
Snow White looked horrible in that one
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Hey, my friend. The friend is
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
The friend is
Because it's not a bad book. It's just it's like it's like my it's like my show book and it's like I'd like to have everybody
That's part of the show in the book. It's a bridge at least one time. It's like a death. No, it's not. No, it's not
I said it says it says you're right next to Jamie's Cowboys and Oliver it says God he's dead. Alison's got he's standard mod
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh
They must be in the garage
I don't know if it's either a carport or a pergola.
Grumple should introduce himself first.
Probably underneath a porch, if I'm being honest.
Oh, yeah, Paige, go to the car.
You're better reception in the car.
Reason weed out of the car.
You disappeared on the show.
There's an antenna in the car.
You hear that?
He's freezing a little bit.
I don't know your major signals a little bit wonky. I'm not sure the page. You're in the book. I'll put Spindela
I'll put you in there. Oh, I will cripple stills. Can you want to be in there? Yeah?
So I just write
Yeah, but if something happens to you, the feds are going to come to get that book and they're going to see all my names in it.
This book is my insurance policy. I'm just going to write Grumple Stilts. It's not his legal name.
Who's that guy? I know that fucking voice.
No, that's my legal name.
It is?
Okay, that's just weird.
Is it a Jewish name or her French? French. Let's make it French. Okay, still skin. Okay. I've never heard that name
It's Austrian
Legally easy. No, maybe not damn psyche. I'll go play with
It's an Austrian name, but I was adopted so super weird situation
I was kind of okay. Can I call you grump grump? I mean grump is a mouthful. Are you a gamer?
Grumps
we've hung out at least twice before and that's fine
He looks like a gamer
We all think karaoke for like two hours one night
You want to keep playing I
Went and started up a stream to do the karaoke and now that's a thing that I'm doing
I don't mean to copy like no, I can't do it
I've got really good feedback on it, too, and like there's a there's a way to do it
Like yeah, the correct way to do it is that whoever is going to sing is that person has to present
so that it's it's matched up and
I mean otherwise you got to rely on really low lag and even that's still gonna be off
But everybody's had a really good time with it. Now. I have to thank you for that idea
100% yeah
Yeah, I have to do I'm more careful with like play music
But but I think like you know in my experience because I have played music and stuff like when you play carry the karaoke music
You know, I think almost 100% of the time
The only thing that's got an actual demonetization strike is
Highway to hell like a CDC and yeah, you just cut that out and then it's gone. Yeah, it's no biggie. Yeah
But what do you say
Destinations wrong. Oh, yeah, I got a second phone 70s. I think I'm a
Yeah, I don't know if it's from final destination, but it was it's an old song. I think right, okay
Okay, good super funny thing about highway to hell is I just wait is this what we went over last time is
You listen to the third line of it
Season ticket on a one-way ride is not the line, but yeah
They were like listening to that one lyric I remember that when they're
They thought they were taking the n-word right there or something and they get rid of different things. Yeah
Hey, psyche you play my sauce
I can't I can't play music got it. I would love it all you know, it's an original size
It's not a I know I know I know but I can't just leave so many streams today. I'll do it like on another stream
How many times you got caught just a yes or no
No, no, it's just complicated because I was like, you know, I would like to but it's like it's probably
But when we times like, you know, you know, like
I got feels like if you know there's just things there's it wasn't a porn bummery thing
I would say it was it were even any like really bad language. It was just
The threatening that you know Alex was threatening and then calling electric bitch and like interesting and then you know and I know
No, I know I know I know I know no man. Nobody didn't mean to
Like you guys you can't show firearms and he got a flashed a gun this year and so
That was you can you can have them on a stream you can't touch them on a live stream
He knows all the rules obviously dudes doing like doing like pew streams or not streams
But pew videos, but you can't on YouTube on a live stream
You can't touch them you can have in the background you can have them being seen a hundred percent
You just can't you can't handle you can't touch them. This guy knows all the fucking rules. This is great
Yeah
Well, I mean, I just I do know like, you know, like one night they had Tracy and pay I think before I was monetized and so
But they were like a Tracy was showing like huge or huge guns
Do they try to pump on your on your panel
No, no. All right. So we gotta get over there. Watch out. All right. The phone bomb is coming. I'm just saying
He's trying to save our corn bomber. He won't end up using his tiny mind to influence you
I usually use discord, but
My own content, but yeah, a lot of times I will do like a stream yard panel, but
I mean, good luck. I wish you luck in your endeavor, sir
Can we let him speak and introduce themselves? That's right. Yeah, go ahead
Well, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I
Yeah, we had to come inside because we have a tin roof on the deck
And we were sitting out in the nice lights in the ambiance, but we're gonna eat live by mosquitoes in the service
Was it was there a cat on the tin roof? Is there a cat on it?
I'm not just kidding, that's a really bad joke.
Well, normally the cats love it up there.
Normally I'm up there.
Rain on the chin roof is one of the best things ever
to fall asleep to.
Am I like?
You fall asleep on the roof.
Oh, I totally agree with you.
That sound?
You like that sound?
Yeah.
Why don't you roll over and fall up there?
No, 100%.
That's one of the best.
That and like a fog horn in the background
and like a little bit of lightning that's
or thunder, that's the best sounds to fall.
You look at the windows of foggy.
You think of something.
I think of the best when I see fog.
I mean, maybe it was maybe it was how I grew up
More powerful of this storm the better because we charge ourselves like this electric energy the earth is like it's natural charging
Just like for your crystals for yourself. It's beautiful. It's cleansing every time there's a storm and make sure to have my crystal
Prairie page. Are you doing electroculture or are you talking about something else?
like a vortex it's where you use uh like you make like copper coils and
harness electricity and makes your your vegetables grow bigger oh yeah you can do that and then
like or go that's how glass certain glass like lightning glass is made yo yo yo that's a real
thing grampou that's a real thing i'll send that video to my sister and she said she produced way more
Yeah, no, I've seen it in real life. Well, like people use it. It's called electroculture, but ball lightning electroculture
Yeah, that's what it's called and it helps don't grow even more
It doesn't even need like lightning to us. It's just using coils to harness
and be into electricity and put it into the soil where the roots of the vegetables you're growing are.
Are we allowed to wish death on people you're a vegetable?
No.
Okay, okay, I just want to be clear.
I'm not sure if that's how it actually works or why, but I don't know that.
That's on the vegetables?
What?
It's just a case, just in case, you know.
You want to curse your veggies and your fruits?
You just write it down on a piece of paper or like where you meet. I don't swear. No, that's where you just write it down on the silence that we don't hear.
There's a thing called a mute button and then you can yell all you want God. You can say everything you want on that mute button.
I don't yell actually. I don't speak loud like you do.
I think he wants to curse me, but why?
Right now I just cursed you out. What I said in the background was blank blank blank blank blank blank blank blank.
and then got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got got
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
Hey
Hello
Why do you have two Apple charging cables
Now hug each other
American
What
Canadian pies not a thing that's not like I don't I demand proof. That's not a thing
Sikes but I want you to put it back on like normal like how it's normal when roll up there. Yeah, like that
You can't see what sorry Sikes
There's not really many people on camera, but yeah
I'm pretty good
That's how I saw you. You were doing mushrooms in their car. How is it?
Actually P
Since I was upside down in the past just see and I'm told you it's like
He's like where's the weed and he's like oh
It's outside of my ground somewhere. He's like, oh look for it. They left the car
I I don't know if you were found the weed, but it blew away or so that was like which way on over there
did find the media. Okay. Yeah. I'm I'm sorry. I am a bit hard of hearing. Did I hear somebody blue
ale also? Blue ale. Oh, what are all you guys doing that we can't?
What are you trying for the weekend?
I don't know.
Are all your guys ants above the waist?
Party on Saturday.
I'm waiting for death.
I'm playing below the waist.
I'm going down below the ways. Oh my god
The wait till we go backstage after the show to show me what's
I'm just kidding. I'm going to be honest with you.
Will there be a Diddy Party page?
Yeah.
Yeah, but you have to party with me in there, Rogue Nomad.
I don't think you want to come.
I'm here. I'm here.
I hear you.
Yeah, you can't keep them. You're you're white
That's the beauty of the party
Lubrication of some sort of fashion I recommend
You need you need the pink you need the pink baby oil it just has the right amount of cocaine
I mean, 500 degree, you know, freedom unit smoke make the, the kitchen full of smoke and use that as
a light tattoo on my back.
Lou. Okay. Where are we going to loop? I don't want to be finished with it.
What? What?
It doesn't, it doesn't look like God. It looks like God and I'm wearing a paper bag over my head.
No, no, no, no.
I apologize.
Is this a Luminati joke, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal, it's not normal,
Well, some people aren't comfortable doing that. That's okay. We're all just here like
God is never cammed up. I've seen easy picture
Oh, yeah, I never saw you though. I got videos online
I got videos online if you want to find me if you want to find me. I got videos online psyche
I don't hide nothing
My hair is a mess right now.
You can follow me, psyche.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not AI.
My hair is trash.
I'm sorry.
There you are.
Oh, hello.
I've seen you first.
I'm AI.
He's shuffling us.
There you go.
Hi, bud.
He froze.
He froze already.
He was like.
I made a ticker board.
I made a ticker board pattern.
Patterns.
$10.
I'm sorry, I'm hard of hearing what what was the name of Mende
Grumple still get yes, ma'am
All right, we have a we have we have we have all the stairs here
It's page and sender Cinderella
Spam SP
I'm just gonna call her Ella
Call them call them Tony and Janet like from three
Okay
Hey, it's just that you know, it's a selling point
Any butane or moose just saying
Open a kitchen we'll call it the we'll call it the Canadian box house
Yeah
She literally has a moose head on her wall. She literally has a moose man. She killed the moose. I think
I mean, I don't wait hang on am I am I blind? Do I not see it or is it not?
The moose is at something real
How would I know that if it's not because what I can see
My bad I didn't I didn't know
It's all over the left.
And you're, I kiss you.
The Moose's name was Bo Wacoal.
It was in love with the squirrel.
And then one day, Paige just came in and came in.
Wait, Rocket J. Squirrel, you messed like,
do you know Rocky?
I think Rocky's mounted above her fireplace.
I don't know, now she's talking.
I for the like couple years I went I like went and attended college
Rocket J. Squirrel was
Freshman freshman class. We said a friend leave the house and we want to make sure he's okay
Cuz they live in the middle of nowhere
Are you back, okay? Hey, this is Rocky J. Squirrel massive of your fireplace. I just one question. Oh, she's left. Okay. Well, it's too late
Is noose on squirrel
I preferred worse than Natasha. I thought Bo Winkle was a little bit dumb and Rocky was a little bit too cocky.
I don't remember any of the actual show that Rocky and Bo Winkle were actually doing.
with what now big Misha
She's the famous black celebrity. She's six or
She's the mother of the
The mother of what me don't know. I'm sorry. I'm hard of hearing I got the volume like as high up
Like he's a tarot card reader. He's trans
I know
These people are just statements of my imagination. Like he was messing with me the whole time
It's okay. It's fine to believe in there was a guy who was messing with us that apparently like
We all were big fans of some lady named big niche and her son that we all
some guy some guy like that like you you're you're the some guy that
Okay, oh, no, give it away
Hey, hey, how are you?
Sorry, thanks for lit me up
You're welcome. How are you?
Who's that voice? That's that's Ray and there's
And let's see and yeah
Played as big niche it
He did. Oh, it was you Ray. What? It's you Ray. I like your name. It reminds me of the sun. Okay, so Michael says quantum experience, quantum expensive, quantum extensive,
Paraphysics 52 only. Is there a picture of a hot dog? I don't know what's going on. Hold on. And then here's Dina. Dina's here.
Oh my god. Oh my god.
Oh my god.
Are you there?
Because we love you.
We do.
I got it. I got it. I have the same.
I
Cue my favorite
You're a little irate
He's reading the charts
I'm good Gotti. How are you? No, that's not a good birthday month
That was that was JT today. That was JT beater. I'm good though
Oh
You guys are the same then
Well, I just wanted to just come and say hi the world nomad his birthday and then gondoled the bundle
Trivia and like family feud gondoled their grumble whatever his channel is
I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer and I'm a bad streamer
it's like thank you just real quick question is your name on discord zephyr
no it's
It's like the way kids that zephyr's mission the name of the west wind though it's the name of the west wind
And psyche psyche is related to zephyr because zephyr carries psyche in the in the in the myth
He carries her over the cliff just keep his powers
so
message me when I think was the tarot reading that you gave me like
meanings and stuff. Did it change your life forever?
I'm not sure. I haven't it was a very it's a very tall block of text. I can't believe it
Are you LH2? I can't believe it myself. I don't know what that is
Hey, man. Oh, we page back home
Hey, it's here. Oh my god
Bestie time
Here you must this will see where I've just been on
Uh, you know, and I have like a pool panel. So I'm doing this. I'm doing this at least I grumble wants to play
I mean, I can leave if you want to thank you. No, no, no, no, I like I like heavy
Yeah
I just want to be with
Who did what?
The one with the yoyo
Michael Houdou
He's interested in this game
and more viewing
Michael Houdou
Are you like in a conspiracy
with us?
Yes Michael, do you see what he's using?
Do you see what he's using?
I have God. We've got two. I'll
No
Everybody's seeing at the same time
I'm trying to talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to the lady, let me talk to
Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not
it doesn't help that your mic sucks
you're bringing chaos
guys, guys, guys
can everybody just view for a second
like an application
it might not gonna work
he's about to lose his fucking mind
hold on, guys
And I get the women's psychic readings.
Y'all shut the fuck up.
Why get these women's psychic readings?
It's about the bone bomb.
We're up here.
OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, I have one condition.
Just drink some water and come down.
Drink some water and come down.
This is so nice.
How do they use the feathers to play?
Let's start with the woman on right.
OK, Michael, your microphone is really bad, though.
And so I don't know if you can, like, fix your mic.
It's like, because it's like, it's not going to be that.
It's not working out Michael, it's working out.
He sounds like shit!
Michael sounds like shit!
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I see. Michael. Michael. Michael.
I can't hear grumble stills can play in the guitar. And I thank you for sharing such positive energy with me. That's not a surprise. No, it's okay.
Well, we do want to read the two women right there in the chat right here. Okay. I bet you do.
Okay, go ahead. Go ahead. Go ahead. I'll put you on the top floor.
Put you on the top floor. There you go. There you go.
To the both of y'all have questions
I don't think they had any questions. We just want to talk to the women. Okay. What why do you have a city, Mike?
She's bathing in that stuff
you're just enjoying their feathers and everything
breathe it in breathe it in
I don't think they want to
they don't want to be harassed by you
I don't think they want to be harassed by you
I
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god
That guy's unhinged. Why is he yelling at us?
Some of us wanted to hear what page and a girlfriend had to say
If you if you stop nagging at him and let him say what you have to say you would have said it in any
No, you was running your mouth the most I
Agree why don't I feel like coming detention Rena?
Because you've been drinking what I don't know what is going on you start trouble with everyone
Michael whoever you are
I'm not judging. Let's just play Michael. Huh? I don't want to be judgmental. I apologize. Shut up and let, shut up and let Paige speak.
Listen y'all, pray for the truth.
I'm just making the most of it.
There's too many people.
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I
Listen, they can sleep on with the same man and listen both of them been sleeping with the same man
Darling he's making
I
Want to say it's like he keeps saying like
That's me
you didn't know
You know, maybe one person at a time speaking because otherwise nobody can understand
No, I would not know that wouldn't be chaotic enough. I think everyone should be
Yeah
The rage was there with the girlfriend and oh
Manneering over each other
We don't have to imagine it we can
Shout out sober one we just have to fuck it up
Yeah
Yeah, guys because pages back and I didn't like what Michael was saying and so I took him off stage
Intel beaters shut up
He was saying that you had been down sleeping with the same man. I know we're like that. We're usually saying weird stuff
That's what he's saying. That's what he said
Yeah, I should tell him to shut up you should tell him to shut up
They've been sleeping with the same man and they've been kind of
your government like it
over the same man that they've been sleeping with
can you tell me something
whoever said that about
like anybody on the panel
you guys are weird
can I hear you
please shut up let's hear what
the two of them have to say
oh they'll be sleeping with the same man
she's not talking
Oh, cool, like, sis, first act, please.
Shut up, beat up, shut up!
It's not even me talking, it's Paige right now.
Can you just write this straight, asshole?
Hey, Paige, Paige, this isn't just talking right now.
It's the guy that's giving the reading, right?
Oh, the shirt's talking, huh?
Oh, yeah, the reading.
It's the guy that's giving the reading.
I'm not going to give a reading right now.
Yeah, I do not give a reading, yeah.
What the fuck is this?
I can read both of them.
Why do we have a dick on the panel?
What is this?
Put Paige off there, not that.
You're going to have to take her down, Psyche.
No, no, no, no, Psyche, you're going to have to take her.
No, not me, sir.
You're going to have to take her down.
Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Psyche, hi, girls, hi, hi, hey.
So, let's get rid of this.
They don't know this.
Let's talk. Let's talk.
Please let us here with...
Please let us here with
paying chance to say...
It's not gonna be probably
it's not gonna be a reading. I'm telling you this right now.
First of all, this is
my best friend and her husband
is my fucking family member.
So we are not fucking the same guy.
I keep saying they're weird.
What? Who said what?
They're weird. I'm like defending them and they say shut up. Be that shut up page like we're the only three females on the panel
Yeah
We're all here. We're all here on the same panel for one reason.
Guys, guys, guys, guys, I think I'll post a couple of people up there.
We're all here on the same panel for one reason, in case I...
Yeah.
What's what's your panel about right now? I'm okay. Yeah, so I
look at again again. Hey, Payton's been deli. You just get a
person to kick off the panel for five minutes so you guys can
have a little bit of more
We're space to talk. Can I can I take one off? Yes, let's see. Let's see the layout. Let's see the layout.
Let's see the layout. Okay, the layout. Okay, so one of the angels, okay, so Paige, which one do you want to ask?
Oh, I mean, I'm going to add these back. I'm going to add them back and you have to see it. These count. These count. Okay.
Shut up
See you guys you get to kick out one of the Barkers
Like
We're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just like, we're just
Who is that? Who is that? Who is that? Who's screaming? Who is that guy?
You don't need to argue you can just do a card reading now. It's all calm
We're gonna kick ourselves
Okay, then I'll leave you because I'm not gonna fight for you
Imagine like I'm just like fucking trying to get a third-party reading for somebody from page
I
Know
Go over there because she's this way in life. Do you go to her pages? You're gonna do a review over there, okay?
I remember you over there, you know
I
Calm down. Yeah. Yeah. Wow. You are a little bit of a
line. Yeah. Yeah. You are a little bit of a line. Yeah.
the
I got some walls now, I got some lugs, look at psych, look at psych, I got some lugs, look at psych, I got some lugs, look at psych, I got some lugs, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look at psych, look
That's that nigga Michael
Do you think maybe the tarot cards can tell him where he can get a new Mike
Be the he can't be the what's all page on what I mean psyche put in the back chat put in the private chat
Is this a mark and look a prairie page?
Are you okay?
I can't read your tarot cards, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot card, you're not a good tarot
Come on, come on, go backstage.
Come on, side, go backstage.
Sam's cool, dawg.
I thought it was Sam, too.
Go with your stalker.
Exploit for the good black magic on you
and go ask him for a carry, okay?
I'm reading.
Wow.
I don't need cars to read this person.
Them ladies right there, I don't need cars.
I already read them right now.
Shut up, yo. Fix your mic.
Shut up, man.
Yeah, you're safe later up. She want to talk later up. Let's see what's up
Okay
Oh
Now let's put it in uranium shots fired
No, no
Go ahead. You said it. You did it. He's like, no, race.
That's racist. I'm confused.
Say, princess, princess, princess is racist.
You're a goofy. Thank you.
See
I'll cook here. Okay, you guys can get up. I don't need I don't need your input right now you little monkeys, okay?
Give me a lump
Wow guys
Talk about bite or I mean, jeez
Yeah, I got a damn man. Look at that. But guys, you know how calm it is now, you know, you know, it's screaming all the time
It was her. You know, I noticed it was her screaming all the time
I mean, it's quite now
Okay, hey, I was like everybody talking like bring him back man
But I just build with them and they're gonna be mad at me and
Oh, absolutely, that's why I do it at comps. I told you at calm times that apparently I don't even know how to do tarot
Sturks that was
So you Michael you do CIA readings is something like that. Yeah, I do see I do see I even as yeah
Can you do can you do a reading for me?
Yeah, what's up? What you want?
Whatever whatever yeah, whatever you can tell me about myself that you shouldn't know that would be perfect
now give me a lot of value in trying to get multiple people to do readings because then if a lot of them's like
They say the kind of same thing
Why'd you screen so much psyche? Oh you want this okay?
Like why are you screaming like a fucking like wild batchy tonight?
Why are you screaming like a bitch tonight?
Screaming
Okay, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it better than you, I know, I can't do it
Emma this year Emma doesn't
Those to be the backstage
She's an unpleasant chef the soup is terrible. I'm sending it back. I'm not having dessert
He's doing his laughing like a hyena and insulting me that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that
I'll put myself backstage with you and we'll have a freak off. How about that?
Is that what you just need to fucking are just what you're agitated about?
Yes, I'm just actually frustrated because I want your boobs so bad.
Oh, what?
Are you
That was an accident
Look at this face this face that's what it's about guys
That's what it's all about I just wanted that I want to see that face and then I'm I'm fine
No, but all reality psyche I do better better tarot cards in you. I don't even have tarot cards
Okay, bitch. It's okay. I'd probably be better.
Oh, you call me a bitch?
Yeah, you call me a bitch?
You call me a pussy? A faggot?
You call me everything. You're getting all the way into it.
It's all your time. I'm allowed to say anything I want now.
I'm allowed.
I'm sorry. I just realized that my head
without my headphones on is shaped like a rectangle.
I'm an actual cartoon character.
Oh, I knew it.
You should have, like, made a mouth
that had your ears cut off or something, but...
You're fine
We're just we're focusing on how fucking silly fucking psyche is tonight. Oh my gosh
You guys
They beat our roads. They beat our roads. They beat our roads.
Just pick on me, guys. Just pick on me. Okay?
Oh, Rob. Oh, I'm happy to just have a kind of ticket.
Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob. Your humor is so stale.
It's okay, psyche. It's okay.
Yeah, these unoriginal, they're such unoriginal scrolls.
Like, who are these people?
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
i was protecting page everybody all the men were like talking over page and like uh you know
her girl and i was like everybody let the ladies talk and then like he got jealous and he spas
out he's like no j1 and michael needs to talk he was like decorating as always i was like right
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I said be the page and Spinderella
Please pick a person to remove for the panel because there's ten people and everyone's talking over each other and this lady's choice
That turn into I'm tick ready. Okay. It's a good idea
I don't want to say that's what you say
I say and then I said let's do it
I got to do it.
You didn't get it.
You didn't choose anybody.
I took myself off and two of them.
You're supposed to say trauma queen.
Psyche.
You made me laugh.
You want none of this cook
That's why you turn gay by the way
Wait, you probably made that marinara sauce. That was your blood wasn't it?
Tell me you never made the spaghetti, you knew the recipe
Tell me you never made spaghetti for your boyfriend
Did you make it beta
Yeah, you know that you are served. No, no, I just made a regular
You only deal with acting wacky crazy bitches that would put fucking weird shit in your spaghetti like a delicacy
I don't even know what would be my food. There'd be like some kind of law hum the law.
You're fishing for your life, bitch.
There would be catfish tacos and they would taste fishy.
I don't know. What?
I don't know. I don't know.
What?
I don't know. It was a bad show.
What oh, oh, I got a whoa
I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I
You know
What did you call me they're gonna send the FBI over here, man
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Who needs better to have a a Alexander McQueen better to die on it?
That's some terror shit right there
She's just had something about that